freepowerboards.com 2008-12-16

# FreePowerBoards - Free phpBB3 Forum Hosting

## **Privacy Policy**

It is the policy of the Alberta Real Estate Association (AREA) that personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is private and confidential. Because your privacy is important to us, the association maintains privacy policies to protect your personal information. 

**Website Privacy Policy**

By using this site, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your consent or as required by law.

**The Information We Collect**

(1) Site Activity Data

Each time a visitor comes to this website, our web server collects and logs certain information. These access logs are kept for a reasonable period of time. These logs include, but are not restricted to your machine’s TCP/IP address, your username (if applicable), date, time and files accessed. These logs also contain information about ‘referrer’ information if you clicked on an external link to an AREA webpage. These logs are used solely for performance, site administration and security reviews. They are not sold or shared in any way to third party organizations.

(2) Cookies

Portions of the AREA website may use cookies only for security and authentication purposes. This information is used solely to maintain your computer’s session to the AREA server. This information is not shared or sold to third party organizations for any purpose.

(3) Personal Information

Personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is collected only when you voluntarily provide it. Such information is received when you send an email through the site or make some other specific contact, such as completing an online form or registering for a course.

The personal information you provide to the association is forwarded only to the person or department equipped to handle your request and is used only to respond to your inquiry.

Personal information will not be sold to any third parties, nor will such information be added to bulk email lists.

**Policy Revisions**

Any changes to the association's privacy policy will be promptly communicated on this website. Policy changes will not alter how we handle previously submitted personal information.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies or wish to update any of the personal information you have provided to us please [contact us](http://www.freepowerboards.com/support/index.php?_m=tickets&_a=submit).
